

PROFILE

Web Developer with 9 years of experience for multiple domains including business, healthcare, e-commerce, etc.

Blockchain developer with 4 years of experience for Dapps, NFT, Web3 projects etc.

Skilled in ether.js and web3.js with hardhat and truffle

LINK

<u>website</u>

CONTACT

Address:

914 Queens Plate Dr Etobicoke, Ontario(ON) Canada

PHONE:

(805) 214-8119

EMAIL:

jasonli890218@gmail.com

LANGUGAE

English

HOBBIES

Football Piano

JASON LINDSAY

Blockchain Developer 4 years Full Stack Engineer 5 years Web Developer 9 years

EDUCATION

Western University

August 2008 – May 2013

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Modea (Junior Web Developer)

May 2013 - March 2017

Developed web application frontends related with healthcare using React.js and Vue.js.

John Abbott College (Full Stack Developer)

March 2017 - June 2018

Built frontends for several projects using React.js and Vue.js and backends using node.is

Chainalysis Inc (Blockchain Developer)

June 2018 - May 2020

Developed smart contracts with Solidity using Remix and Hardhat to deploy on several blockchain networks Created and deployed ERC20, ERC721 tokens to blockchain networks

Pharos Production (Full Stack Developer)

May 2020 - June 2022

Built frontend and backend for Dapps, NFT and Web3 projects based on ethereum network using React.js, Redux, Vue.js, Web3.js and Ether.js according to requirements and development guidelines

SKILLS

